mmaroot.com 2010-06-19

# Privacy Policy

It is the policy of MMA Root that personal information, such as your name, or email address is private and confidential. Because your privacy is important to us, the site maintains privacy policies to protect your personal information. View our site’s Privacy Policy.

**Website Privacy Policy**  
By using this site, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your consent or as required by law.

**The Information We Collect**  
**(1) Site Activity Data**  
Each time a visitor comes to this website, our web server collects and logs certain information. These access logs are kept for a reasonable period of time. These logs include, but are not restricted to your machine’s TCP/IP address, your username (if applicable), date, time and files accessed. These logs also contain information about ‘referrer’ information if you clicked on an external link to an AREA webpage. These logs are used solely for performance, site administration and security reviews. They are not sold or  
shared in any way to third party organizations.  
**(2) Cookies**  
Portions of the MMA Root website may use cookies only for security and authentication  
purposes. This information is used solely to maintain your computer’s session to the AREA  
server. This information is not shared or sold to third party organizations for any purpose.

**(3)   Personal Information **  
Personal information, such as your name, personal postal and email address, or personal telephone number is collected only when you voluntarily provide it. Such information is received when you send an email through the site or make some other specific contact, such as completing an online form. The personal information you provide to the association is forwarded only to the person or department equipped to handle your request and is used only to respond to your inquiry. Personal information will not be sold to any third parties, nor will such information be added to bulk email lists.

**Policy Revisions**  
Any changes to the association’s privacy policy will be promptly communicated on this website. Policy changes will not alter how we handle previously submitted personal information. If you have any questions about our privacy policies or wish to update any of the personal information you have provided to us, contact the association’s privacy compliance officer at privacypolicy@mmaroot.com.
